<health-log>
	<source>
		<type>chatlog</type>
		<application>keybase</application>
		<channel>private chat</channel>
	</source>
	<entry>
		<entry-metadata>
			<user>ultimape</user>
			<datetime>
				<time>12:58 PM</time>
				<date>12 Aug 2021</date>
			</datetime>
		</entry-metadata>
		<entry-text><![CDATA[
I am going to start my dog feces FMT sometime at the end of the month. Hoping to aim toward the 20th. Going to be interesting.
I could get sepsis and die.
I have been learning about how gut bacteria might help with dna repair. It makes me wonder if they can help.
]]>
		</entry-text>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<entry-metadata>
			<user>ultimape</user>
			<datetime>
				<time>9:34 AM</time>
				<date>14 Aug 2021</date>
			</datetime>
		</entry-metadata>
		<entry-text><![CDATA[
If I'm wrong about the dog shit. i'm probably going to die.
I'm scared.
:(
]]>
		</entry-text>
	</entry>

	<entry>
		<entry-metadata>
			<user>ultimape</user>
			<datetime>
				<time>1:39 AM</time>
				<date>1 Jan 2022</date>
			</datetime>
		</entry-metadata>
		<entry-text><![CDATA[
Started the dog shit trial.
]]>
		</entry-text>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<entry-metadata>
			<user>ultimape</user>
			<datetime>
				<time>12:40 PM</time>
				<date>1 Jan 2022</date>
			</datetime>
		</entry-metadata>
		<entry-text><![CDATA[
(asked: what will I be measuring?)
Heart rate, body temp, blood pressure, SPO2, hand strength.
]]>
		</entry-text>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<entry-metadata>
			<user>ultimape</user>
			<datetime>
				<time>12:14 AM</time>
				<date>2 Jan 2022</date>
			</datetime>
		</entry-metadata>
		<entry-text><![CDATA[
hand strength, body composition shifts.  If i'm right about how this works, i will have improvements over a 6 month period as my body starts to trigger different epigenetic pathways.
I should be able to balance on one leg regularly and not stumble to the bathroom.
]]>
		</entry-text>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<entry-metadata>
			<user>ultimape</user>
			<datetime>
				<time>12:16 AM</time>
				<date>2 Jan 2022</date>
			</datetime>
		</entry-metadata>
		<entry-text><![CDATA[
(asked: do I have a body composition scale?)
yeah. I need batteries tho and need a place to use it.
gonna get that in a day or two
]]>
		</entry-text>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<entry-metadata>
			<user>ultimape</user>
			<datetime>
				<time>12:16 AM</time>
				<date>2 Jan 2022</date>
			</datetime>
		</entry-metadata>
		<entry-text><![CDATA[
I go a wiThings scale, it seemed pretty reliable
]]>
		</entry-text>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<entry-metadata>
			<user>ultimape</user>
			<datetime>
				<time>12:17 AM</time>
				<date>2 Jan 2022</date>
			</datetime>
		</entry-metadata>
		<entry-text><![CDATA[
(asked: any chemical tests?)
I have an acetoacetate one to see if I get into ketosis, but that's mostly to see if i'm getting sick
]]>
		</entry-text>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<entry-metadata>
			<user>ultimape</user>
			<datetime>
				<time>12:18 AM</time>
				<date>2 Jan 2022</date>
			</datetime>
		</entry-metadata>
		<entry-text><![CDATA[
This is mostly a safety trial so i'm not to worried on tests
i'm gonna pick up some things I saw at walmart that can tell me drugs etc. Not sure what else they have.  walgreends didn't have anything useful.
I only took one pill so far and i'm waiting a few days to see if I get GI response before trying another
]]>
		</entry-text>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<entry-metadata>
			<user>ultimape</user>
			<datetime>
				<time>12:20 AM</time>
				<date>2 Jan 2022</date>
			</datetime>
		</entry-metadata>
		<entry-text><![CDATA[
(asked: how was the dog?)
Dog ended up getting diarhea, but we also gave her too much of that teef thing at the same time.  She was good when we stopped the teef for a bit
]]>
		</entry-text>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<entry-metadata>
			<user>ultimape</user>
			<datetime>
				<time>12:31 AM</time>
				<date>2 Jan 2022</date>
			</datetime>
		</entry-metadata>
		<entry-text><![CDATA[
(asked: how are you planning to protect yourself if you get sick?)
I spent the last few months looking at antibiotic herbs and its why I made that honey garlic. I can use that, and bunch of red wine to clear my intestinal tract and then go on a fast. The wine will boost ketone levels and the garlic will flow thru my blood attacking the bacteria (if it gets in).  Fasting also works well to fight bacterial infections.
]]>
		</entry-text>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<entry-metadata>
			<user>ultimape</user>
			<datetime>
				<time>12:37 AM</time>
				<date>2 Jan 2022</date>
			</datetime>
		</entry-metadata>
		<entry-text><![CDATA[
(asked: what about antibiotics?)
I looked into a bunch of stuff I could get, but they all risk getting in my blood stream (even the ones that aren't supposed to) because of the crohn's issue. I'm taking a lot of care to eat in a way that maximizes my gut barrier, but if something did slip thru, the garlic + red wine seems to be comparable to stuff I could buy.
I do have access to some tho if I need it.
]]>
		</entry-text>
	</entry>

	<entry>
		<entry-metadata>
			<user>ultimape</user>
			<datetime>
				<time>9:16 PM</time>
				<date>2 Jan 2022</date>
			</datetime>
		</entry-metadata>
		<entry-text><![CDATA[
(asked: status?)
I am fine
]]>
		</entry-text>
	</entry>

	<entry>
		<entry-metadata>
			<user>ultimape</user>
			<datetime>
				<time>6:29 AM</time>
				<date>3 Jan 2022</date>
			</datetime>
		</entry-metadata>
		<entry-text><![CDATA[
(asked: why are you doing this yourself?)
I can't make it to doctors appointments becaus of my non-24-hour and gave up
realized I could just research it myself, already having a lot of knowelge because of my mom's health issues meaning I needed to know a bit
]]>
		</entry-text>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<entry-metadata>
			<user>ultimape</user>
			<datetime>
				<time>3:08 PM</time>
				<date>3 Jan 2022</date>
			</datetime>
		</entry-metadata>
		<entry-text><![CDATA[
Just woke up. I am doing fine. So far the only abberation has been a minor of a headache the first day. May have been unrelated, but I'm going to pay attention to it when I take the next pill.
]]>
		</entry-text>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<entry-metadata>
			<user>ultimape</user>
			<datetime>
				<time>2:43 AM</time>
				<date>4 Jan 2022</date>
			</datetime>
		</entry-metadata>
		<entry-text><![CDATA[
Doing good today. I jus took my second pill. Gonna wait another 3 days before I take them more often.
]]>
		</entry-text>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<entry-metadata>
			<user>ultimape</user>
			<datetime>
				<time>12:43 PM</time>
				<date>5 Jan 2022</date>
			</datetime>
		</entry-metadata>
		<entry-text><![CDATA[
(asked: why did you miss a day?)
My sleep schedule is weird.
]]>
		</entry-text>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<entry-metadata>
			<user>ultimape</user>
			<datetime>
				<time>6:10 AM</time>
				<date>6 Jan 2022</date>
			</datetime>
		</entry-metadata>
		<entry-text><![CDATA[
(asked: headache go away?)
yeah
only had it for a day. I seem to get a bit of a runny nose every time I take it so far, but this is normal for me so IDK
]]>
		</entry-text>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<entry-metadata>
			<user>ultimape</user>
			<datetime>
				<time>5:27 PM</time>
				<date>6 Jan 2022</date>
			</datetime>
		</entry-metadata>
		<entry-text><![CDATA[
All my vitals have been ok. Only issue I run into is my normal retardedness when I haven't slept in a while. If anything my bathroom use is more regular than usual.
My body temp hasn't stopped below 98 F which is also odd. Maybe I've been eating more reliably than normal, tho it doesn't seem like it
]]>
		</entry-text>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<entry-metadata>
			<user>ultimape</user>
			<datetime>
				<time>2:11 AM</time>
				<date>8 Jan 2022</date>
			</datetime>
		</entry-metadata>
		<entry-text><![CDATA[
Still doing fine. Going to take 3rd pill. A bit late, but my sleep is weird.
]]>
		</entry-text>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<entry-metadata>
			<user>ultimape</user>
			<datetime>
				<time>2:12 AM</time>
				<date>8 Jan 2022</date>
			</datetime>
		</entry-metadata>
		<entry-text><![CDATA[
(asked: any improvements?)
Nothing noticable.
trials with autistic types took a month straight of FMT pills for them to take hold IIRC.
]]>
		</entry-text>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<entry-metadata>
			<user>ultimape</user>
			<datetime>
				<time>2:14 AM</time>
				<date>8 Jan 2022</date>
			</datetime>
		</entry-metadata>
		<entry-text><![CDATA[
my gut biome results were pretty fucked. heavy inflammation producting varieties. it also didn't say anything about fungus, which is what I suspect make it not work well for autistics
inflammation = kill gut bacteria.
]]>
		</entry-text>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<entry-metadata>
			<user>ultimape</user>
			<datetime>
				<time>2:40 AM</time>
				<date>8 Jan 2022</date>
			</datetime>
		</entry-metadata>
		<entry-text><![CDATA[
The viome test I took has some cool analysis of my blood. says my metabolic age is 37 despite being 34.  lots of other neat stuff that should get me a pretty impressive showing of a 
 shift if it does anything.
https://keybase.pub/Gut%20Test/Sampled%20September%2026/
direct link to pdf https://ultimape.keybase.pub/Gut%20Test/Sampled%20September%2026/Viome/ViomeRecommendations_F9AEC9229484.pdf
most of it says "not optimal", which sounds about right
the biological age on page 35 is the main one I am expecting to shift as I suspect the gut bacteria will  fix mTOR, IGF-1, Sirtuins, and AMPK. Its fun how they test for that
]]>
		</entry-text>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<entry-metadata>
			<user>ultimape</user>
			<datetime>
				<time>2:44 AM</time>
				<date>8 Jan 2022</date>
			</datetime>
		</entry-metadata>
		<entry-text><![CDATA[
I am predicting it to go from 37 to 32
that was 199 when I bought it. The prices change a lot
]]>
		</entry-text>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<entry-metadata>
			<user>ultimape</user>
			<datetime>
				<time>2:46 AM</time>
				<date>8 Jan 2022</date>
			</datetime>
		</entry-metadata>
		<entry-text><![CDATA[
I got this kit, which does blood and poop https://www.viome.com/products/health-intelligence

They are trying to sell customized vitamin packs as a service.
]]>
		</entry-text>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<entry-metadata>
			<user>ultimape</user>
			<datetime>
				<time>2:47 AM</time>
				<date>8 Jan 2022</date>
			</datetime>
		</entry-metadata>
		<entry-text><![CDATA[
(asked: TMA is good!)
yeah, i'm happy about TMA. that means my heart is probably going to be ok
TMA => TMAO is gut bacteria driven AFAICT. I have been focusing on butyrate, so it makes sense that it would be alright.
I also took a psomagen gut test, but it was more just a second datapoint to confirm that my gut bacteria actually shifted.
they bought ubiome's patents afaict
]]>
		</entry-text>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<entry-metadata>
			<user>ultimape</user>
			<datetime>
				<time>2:31 PM</time>
				<date>8 Jan 2022</date>
			</datetime>
		</entry-metadata>
		<entry-text><![CDATA[
Vitals normal. If anything systolic blood pressure is lower than average.

Going to go to a stressful store after a long drive. Will be a good test of my mood /stress handling.
]]>
		</entry-text>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<entry-metadata>
			<user>ultimape</user>
			<datetime>
				<time>7:39 AM</time>
				<date>11 Jan 2022</date>
			</datetime>
		</entry-metadata>
		<entry-text><![CDATA[
Doing ok. Kinda meh feeling but its not anything out of the ordinary. Vitals are fine.
]]>
		</entry-text>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<entry-metadata>
			<user>ultimape</user>
			<datetime>
				<time>7:49 AM</time>
				<date>11 Jan 2022</date>
			</datetime>
		</entry-metadata>
		<entry-text><![CDATA[
(asked: how long until you see negative effects?)
most of the negative effects would be quick - infection risk. if there were human parasites in the mix that are un accounted for, I'm not sure.
]]>
		</entry-text>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<entry-metadata>
			<user>ultimape</user>
			<datetime>
				<time>7:51 AM</time>
				<date>11 Jan 2022</date>
			</datetime>
		</entry-metadata>
		<entry-text><![CDATA[
Risk of seeing shit (psychosis) would be driven by immune changes, but that should also coincide with fevers and other metabolic changes and GI resposnes.
]]>
		</entry-text>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<entry-metadata>
			<user>ultimape</user>
			<datetime>
				<time>7:53 AM</time>
				<date>11 Jan 2022</date>
			</datetime>
		</entry-metadata>
		<entry-text><![CDATA[
(asked: have a test for mental stuff?)
I  have been making sure I can still talk to GF and she understands my requests. Logging mood and checking my iris dilation
]]>
		</entry-text>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<entry-metadata>
			<user>ultimape</user>
			<datetime>
				<time>7:55 AM</time>
				<date>11 Jan 2022</date>
			</datetime>
		</entry-metadata>
		<entry-text><![CDATA[
been pulling up old games that I know I should remember and seem to be able to use them without much effort.

Played dwarf fortress for a bit today and still had all the hotkeys remembered.
]]>
		</entry-text>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<entry-metadata>
			<user>ultimape</user>
			<datetime>
				<time>7:56 AM</time>
				<date>11 Jan 2022</date>
			</datetime>
		</entry-metadata>
		<entry-text><![CDATA[
I was having issues understand GF before unless I was looking at her mouth. Thats part of the thing I do when I check that she still understands me.
(see if I can understand her without looking at her)
]]>
		</entry-text>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<entry-metadata>
			<user>ultimape</user>
			<datetime>
				<time>7:58 AM</time>
				<date>11 Jan 2022</date>
			</datetime>
		</entry-metadata>
		<entry-text><![CDATA[
understanding things is a good idea. I've only been using https://humanbenchmark.com/tests/reactiontime/
]]>
		</entry-text>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<entry-metadata>
			<user>ultimape</user>
			<datetime>
				<time>3:19 AM</time>
				<date>14 Jan 2022</date>
			</datetime>
		</entry-metadata>
		<entry-text><![CDATA[
still alive. still eating dog shit
]]>
		</entry-text>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<entry-metadata>
			<user>ultimape</user>
			<datetime>
				<time>7:16 PM</time>
				<date>19 Jan 2022</date>
			</datetime>
		</entry-metadata>
		<entry-text><![CDATA[
still alive
]]>
		</entry-text>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<entry-metadata>
			<user>ultimape</user>
			<datetime>
				<time>7:17 PM</time>
				<date>19 Jan 2022</date>
			</datetime>
		</entry-metadata>
		<entry-text><![CDATA[
(asked: Any changes?)
my diet got a bit more shit, but i'm handling it well.
burritos I'm eating are making me slightly constipated, but not as bad as they have in the past.
]]>
		</entry-text>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<entry-metadata>
			<user>ultimape</user>
			<datetime>
				<time>7:25 PM</time>
				<date>19 Jan 2022</date>
			</datetime>
		</entry-metadata>
		<entry-text><![CDATA[
my gut issues make me weird. apple juice has never caused me the shits and cheese has never  constipated me
coffee doens't make me poop (unless I also take nicotine)
]]>
		</entry-text>
	</entry>

	<entry>
		<entry-metadata>
			<user>ultimape</user>
			<datetime>
				<time>2:43 PM</time>
				<date>21 Jan 2022</date>
			</datetime>
		</entry-metadata>
		<entry-text><![CDATA[
I will be visit my dad for bit.
]]>
		</entry-text>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<entry-metadata>
			<user>ultimape</user>
			<datetime>
				<time>6:10 PM</time>
				<date>25 Jan 2022</date>
			</datetime>
		</entry-metadata>
		<entry-text><![CDATA[
will update tomorrow, tired from visiting dad
]]>
		</entry-text>
	</entry>

	<entry>
		<entry-metadata>
			<user>ultimape</user>
			<datetime>
				<time>2:11 AM</time>
				<date>31 Jan 2022</date>
			</datetime>
		</entry-metadata>
		<entry-text><![CDATA[
took a week to recover from my hurting my back at dads.  last time It took 2.5+ to get my head on straight, so that is nice.
so not exactly perfect muscle function, but quick recovery is good because it means I can afford to risk exercising, which was one of my hopes.
]]>
		</entry-text>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<entry-metadata>
			<user>ultimape</user>
			<datetime>
				<time>2:13 AM</time>
				<date>31 Jan 2022</date>
			</datetime>
		</entry-metadata>
		<entry-text><![CDATA[
I also haven't done anything to tweak my diet from normal, so I suspect I'll be doing really good once I focus on doing real keto
i used to only have clear nose only when doing keto, so that it's clear right now without it is also an improvement from baseline.
no crohn's issues really to speak of either after hurting my back. normally muscle damage  = inflammation that triggers a crohn's flair.
so I think thats a good sign it's helping my gut.  This dog shit thing was actually made to treat a form of dog diarrheia, so its not unexpected. But I wasn't confident it would work so well.
]]>
		</entry-text>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<entry-metadata>
			<user>ultimape</user>
			<datetime>
				<time>1:20 AM</time>
				<date>4 Feb 2022</date>
			</datetime>
		</entry-metadata>
		<entry-text><![CDATA[
Yesterday I stood for an hour wihtout fatigue and managed to make food while dealing with a number of things that would normally have me shutdown. I even made a video of it.
(note: personal detail removed)
I ordered the Viome test for taking fecal samples and blood raitings for after. that will give me proof that it worked beyond my own general feeling.
]]>
		</entry-text>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<entry-metadata>
			<user>ultimape</user>
			<datetime>
				<time>1:23 AM</time>
				<date>4 Feb 2022</date>
			</datetime>
		</entry-metadata>
		<entry-text><![CDATA[
Once I do that, i'll be switching to a proper keto diet and see if i gain muscle from exersizing. that will be the big thing that tells me it worked for real.
]]>
		</entry-text>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<entry-metadata>
			<user>ultimape</user>
			<datetime>
				<time>5:42 AM</time>
				<date>4 Feb 2022</date>
			</datetime>
		</entry-metadata>
		<entry-text><![CDATA[
I have made some significant progress on getting a way to write and publish documents on my own website using git + jekyll.

I still have to clean it up a bit more with some features that are missing, but this should soon be available on my wovensoup domain.

I just published a longform essay to see what the Virtual Assistant can find that might help with the stuff I face.
https://ultimape.github.io/garden/weeds/write-drafts/longform/virtual-assistant-needs

This feels pretty significant for me given how unproductive I'd been the past year or so.
]]>
		</entry-text>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<entry-metadata>
			<user>ultimape</user>
			<datetime>
				<time>5:19 AM</time>
				<date>7 Feb 2022</date>
			</datetime>
		</entry-metadata>
		<entry-text><![CDATA[
I thought I was done with the pills, but when I went to dump out the bottle I found an extra one.

Realized after the fact that 30 days * 1.5 hour drift meant I had lost a day somewhere, lol.
I taste tested it since it was supposed to be the last one.

It is vaguely like a mix between a calcium pill ground up, a B-vitamin Complex, and Bile.

I did confirm that when in low concentrations it does in fact smell like flowers.
]]>
		</entry-text>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<entry-metadata>
			<user>ultimape</user>
			<datetime>
				<time>12:46 AM</time>
				<date>8 Feb 2022</date>
			</datetime>
		</entry-metadata>
		<entry-text><![CDATA[
(asked: How long to determine if it didn't work or doesn't hold?)
Last pill today. Then done.
Would expect it to hold for a week before any of the bacteria die off from starvation.
]]>
		</entry-text>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<entry-metadata>
			<user>ultimape</user>
			<datetime>
				<time>3:29 AM</time>
				<date>10 Feb 2022</date>
			</datetime>
		</entry-metadata>
		<entry-text><![CDATA[
(asked: would you have been able to use an EEG?)
Honestly I likely wouldn't have used it. It was hard enough to just get all the stuff together for my vitals.
I had already been delayed by 2 months just with how off I was feeling.
]]>
		</entry-text>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<entry-metadata>
			<user>ultimape</user>
			<datetime>
				<time>3:31 AM</time>
				<date>10 Feb 2022</date>
			</datetime>
		</entry-metadata>
		<entry-text><![CDATA[
(comment: It's good to hear that you are feeling better. It's the middle of the winter so the weather isn't likely to be the reason.)
I don't wanna bust ass right now until I get the second Viome sample. But after I do I'm gonna be spending time actually cleaning my space. It's all a big pile from not being able to lift things. It took me 6 hours just to make sure I had space to keep my measurement tools together.

Huge difference from before
Yeah the weather is worse! But I stopped feeling cold from it. I'm happy about that
]]>
		</entry-text>
	</entry>
</health-log>